Tufts-New England Medical Center Records MS224
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Administration records, 1929 -- 1985; 1970 -- 1980; MS224.002; 20.4 Linear Feet
  - Pine Street Inn, 1970; MS224.002.010.00051 (Box 10)
  - Real Estate, 1970; MS224.002.010.00052 (Box 10)
  - T-NEMC Rental Charges, 1971 -- 1972; MS224.002.010.00053 (Box 10)
  - Rental Space - Properties, 1970 -- 1971; MS224.002.010.00054 (Box 10)
  - Property - Ruggiero Files, 1970; MS224.002.010.00055 (Box 10)
  - 210 South Street, 1975; MS224.002.010.00056 (Box 10)
  - St. James Church, 1970 -- 1974; MS224.002.010.00057 (Box 10)
  - 156 Stuart, 1976; MS224.002.010.00058 (Box 10)
  - 147 West Fourth St., 1977; MS224.002.010.00059 (Box 10)
  - South Cove Property Status and Unit Ownership, 1967 -- 1968; MS224.002.011.00001 (Box 11)
  - Tai Tung Village - Property, 1972; MS224.002.011.00002 (Box 11)
  - Reorganization, 1974 -- 1976; MS224.002.011.00003 (Box 11)
  - City taxes, 1971; MS224.002.011.00004 (Box 11)
  - Zoning - properties, 1970; MS224.002.011.00005 (Box 11)
  - Proposal Original, 1975 -- 1976; MS224.002.011.00006 (Box 11)
  - Revised Proposal D, 1975; MS224.002.011.00007 (Box 11)
  - Position description, 1974; MS224.002.011.00008 (Box 11)
  - Meetings, 1975; MS224.002.011.00009 (Box 11)
  - Organization Proposal - Position Descriptions, MS224.002.011.00010 (Box 11)
  - C and PA Resumes, 1970; MS224.002.011.00011 (Box 11)
  - Personnel - Administration, 1971; MS224.002.011.00012 (Box 11)
  - Personnel - Policies, 1969 -- 1971; MS224.002.011.00013 (Box 11)
  - Expense Account Procedure, 1969 -- 1970; MS224.002.011.00014 (Box 11)
  - Administrator's Report, 1969 -- 1970; MS224.002.011.00015 (Box 11)
  - NEMCH Affirmative Action Program, 1970; MS224.002.011.00016 (Box 11)
  - Boston City Hospital, 1969; MS224.002.011.00017 (Box 11)
  - Hospital Council, 1969 -- 1970; MS224.002.011.00018 (Box 11)
  - Management Meetings, 1969 -- 1970; MS224.002.011.00019 (Box 11)
  - Minority Employment, 1969 -- 1970; MS224.002.011.00020 (Box 11)
  - NEMCH General Data, 1969 -- 1970; MS224.002.011.00021 (Box 11)
  - Personnel - Resumes, 1970; MS224.002.011.00022 (Box 11)
  - Elderly Housing, 1971; MS224.002.011.00023 (Box 11)
  - Medical Center Housing, 1969 -- 1971; MS224.002.011.00024 (Box 11)
  - Brief History: Chinatown and T-NEMC, 1971; MS224.002.011.00025 (Box 11)
  - Hinsey Report, 1959; MS224.002.011.00026 (Box 11)
  - Reorganization - Status, 1973 -- 1976; MS224.002.011.00027 (Box 11)
  - Anna Reinauer Portrait Fund, 1978; MS224.002.011.00028 (Box 11)
  - Roxbury Businessmen's Development Corp., 1971; MS224.002.011.00029 (Box 11)
  - Audio/Visual, 1971; MS224.002.011.00030 (Box 11)
  - Brief History, 1970 -- 1971; MS224.002.011.00031 (Box 11)
  - WCVB-TV Channel 5, 1970 -- 1971; MS224.002.011.00032 (Box 11)
  - Adaptive Housing, 1970 -- 1971; MS224.002.011.00033 (Box 11)
  - Quincy Total Health Project, 1970; MS224.002.011.00034 (Box 11)
  - Social Service Committee for the Chinese Community, 1971; MS224.002.011.00035 (Box 11)
  - Primary Offsite Community Care Centers, 1970; MS224.002.011.00036 (Box 11)
  - Health Care Problems, 1970; MS224.002.011.00037 (Box 11)
  - Spring Event (C & PA), 1970; MS224.002.011.00038 (Box 11)
  - Land Fact Sheet, MS224.002.011.00039 (Box 11)
  - Chinese Community Health Task Force, 1971 -- 1972; MS224.002.011.00040 (Box 11)
  - Community Health Projects Committee, 1970 -- 1972; MS224.002.011.00041 (Box 11)
  - Letter to B.R.A., 1971; MS224.002.011.00042 (Box 11)
  - Evening Clinic, 1970; MS224.002.011.00043 (Box 11)
  - Community - General, 1971 -- 1976; MS224.002.011.00044 (Box 11)
  - Mult-Disease Testing Program in Chinatown, 1970; MS224.002.011.00045 (Box 11)
  - Chinese Christian Church of New England, 1972; MS224.002.011.00046 (Box 11)
  - Chinese Economic Development Council, 1976; MS224.002.011.00047 (Box 11)
  - Jung/Brannen Association Inc. Architects, MS224.002.011.00048 (Box 11)
  - Chinatown Organization, 1972; MS224.002.011.00049 (Box 11)
  - Chinese Community, 1970 -- 1971; MS224.002.011.00050 (Box 11)
  - Chinese Community Council, 1973; MS224.002.011.00051 (Box 11)
  - CACA General, 1970 -- 1974; MS224.002.011.00052 (Box 11)
  - Chinese Health Center, 1969 -- 1974; MS224.002.011.00053 (Box 11)
  - CCHC, 1975 -- 1976; MS224.002.011.00054 (Box 11)
  - Free Chinatown Committee, 1971; MS224.002.011.00055 (Box 11)
  - Boston Chinese Community Health Center, 1976; MS224.002.011.00056 (Box 11)
  - Chinese Community Health Center, 1970 -- 1975; MS224.002.012.00001 (Box 12)
  - Chinese Community Health Center, 1971 -- 1975; MS224.002.012.00002 (Box 12)
  - Married Student Housing, 1971 -- 1972; MS224.002.012.00003 (Box 12)
  - Voice of Chinatown, MS224.002.012.00004 (Box 12)
  - Community English Language Classes, 1972 -- 1974; MS224.002.012.00005 (Box 12)
  - Chinatown Boys' Club, 1973 -- 1975; MS224.002.012.00006 (Box 12)
  - QSC - Joint Board, 1971 -- 1972; MS224.002.012.00007 (Box 12)
  - Tufts-NEMC and its Community, 1971; MS224.002.012.00008 (Box 12)
  - Organization and planning, 1969 -- 1973; MS224.002.012.00009 (Box 12)
  - Quincy School Planning Project, 1970 -- 1971; MS224.002.012.00010 (Box 12)
  - YMCA, 1969 -- 1975; MS224.002.012.00011 (Box 12)
  - B.Y.M.C.V., 1977; MS224.002.012.00012 (Box 12)
  - 7 Man Team Dinner, 1976 -- 1977; MS224.002.012.00013 (Box 12)
  - South Cove YMCA, 1974 -- 1977; MS224.002.012.00014 (Box 12)
  - Housing - Codman/Niles/Nordblom, 1971 -- 1972; MS224.002.012.00015 (Box 12)
  - Housing - Reports, 1971; MS224.002.012.00016 (Box 12)
  - Housing - QSCC, 1970 -- 1972; MS224.002.012.00017 (Box 12)
  - Housing - Sprague, 1971; MS224.002.012.00018 (Box 12)
  - Housing - Chron memos, 1971 -- 1972; MS224.002.012.00019 (Box 12)
  - Housing - Basic Data - Misc. Calc., 1971; MS224.002.012.00020 (Box 12)
  - Quincy School Community Council, 1969 -- 1977; MS224.002.012.00021 (Box 12)
  - Quincy School Community Council, 1971 -- 1977; MS224.002.012.00022 (Box 12)
  - CCBA/CACA, 1969 -- 1971; MS224.002.012.00023 (Box 12)
  - CACA Multi-Service Center - Community Relations, 1971 -- 1974; MS224.002.012.00024 (Box 12)
  - Sampan, 1974; MS224.002.012.00025 (Box 12)
  - CACA Planning Conference, 1971; MS224.002.012.00026 (Box 12)
  - Boston Redevelopment Authority, MS224.002.012.00027 (Box 12)
  - Hospital Auxiliaries and Volunteers Report #3, 1962; MS224.002.012.00028 (Box 12)
  - Classification of Health Care Institute, 1968; MS224.002.013.00001; American Hospital Association (Box 13)
  - New Program in Medical Education at Tufts University, 1968; MS224.002.013.00002 (Box 13)
  - Current Estimates from the Health Interview Survey, 1968; MS224.002.013.00003 (Box 13)
  - Hospitals and Sanatoria in Massachusetts, 1950; MS224.002.013.00004; Commonwealth of Massachusetts Department of Public Health (Box 13)
  - lnstitute on Infectious Diarrhea of the Newborn, 1949; MS224.002.013.00005; Massachusetts Department of Public Helath Division of Maternal and Child Health (Box 13)
  - Transportation Planning MASCO, 1975; MS224.002.013.00006 (Box 13)
  - Study on Cost of Nursing Education, 1964; MS224.002.013.00007; National League for Nursing (Box 13)
  - Report of the Task Force on Relationships Between Tufts University School of Medicine and its Associated Hospitals, 1975; MS224.002.013.00008; Pugh-Roberts Associates, Inc. (Box 13)
  - Tufts University School of Dental Medicine Clinic Operation Survey Report, 1970; MS224.002.013.00009; Tufts-New England Medical Center Planning Office (Box 13)
  - Growing with the New Boston - Don Bosco Technical High School, MS224.002.013.00010 (Box 13)
  - Dental Health Sciences Building, 1973; MS224.002.013.00011 (Box 13)
  - Progressive Architecture, 1972; MS224.002.013.00012; Reinhold (Box 13)
  - How People Feel About Downtown Parking: An Opinion Research Study, MS224.002.013.00013; Downtown Research and Development Center (Box 13)
  - Downtown Malls: 12 Case Studies, MS224.002.013.00014 (Box 13)
  - Tufts University School of Dental Medicine Report: Dental Clinic Equipment and Work Arrangements, 1970; MS224.002.013.00015 (Box 13)
  - TAC no. 72044, 1973; MS224.002.013.00016 (Box 13)
  - Tufts University School of Dental Medicine: Proposal of Dental Clinical Instrument Processing Facilities, 1970; MS224.002.013.00017 (Box 13)
  - Millis Personnel, 1974; MS224.002.013.00018 (Box 13)
  - Report of John S. Millis to the Administrative Board of T-NEMC, 1972; MS224.002.013.00019 (Box 13)
  - New England Medical Center Hospital - Edward Ehrlich and Jack Dunn, 1974; MS224.002.013.00020 (Box 13)
  - Guidelines for Health Services Research and Development Hospital Mergers, 1972; MS224.002.013.00021; U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare National Center for Health Services Research and Development (Box 13)
  - Millis Study - Financial Data, 1973; MS224.002.013.00022 (Box 13)
  - Chapman Task Force, 1971; MS224.002.013.00023; Boston University Medical Center (Box 13)
  - Annual report, 1976 -- 1977; MS224.002.013.00024; Association of American Medical Colleges (Box 13)
  - An Interim Statement, 1977; MS224.002.013.00025; Hospital Research and Educational Trust (Box 13)
  - Association for Academic Health Center (AAHC), 1977 -- 1978; MS224.002.013.00026; Association for Academic Health Centers (Box 13)
  - Sampan, 1978 -- 1980; MS224.002.013.00027; Chinese-American Civic Association (Box 13)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1978; MS224.002.013.00028 (Box 13)
  - Albany Medical Center, MS224.002.013.00029 (Box 13)
  - Financial Task Force, 1975; MS224.002.013.00030 (Box 13)
  - Parking Garage Affirmative Action Plans, 1972; MS224.002.013.00031 (Box 13)
  - A Program for Progress in the 1970s, MS224.002.013.00032; Tufts-New England Medical Center Administrative Committee (Box 13)
  - Millis Study - Financial Data, 1972 -- 1973; MS224.002.013.00033 (Box 13)
  - 1960 Organization Plan, 1960 -- 1972; MS224.002.013.00034 (Box 13)
  - Boston and Beyond, 1974; MS224.002.013.00035 (Box 13)
  - Chinatown Resident's Petition, MS224.002.013.00036 (Box 13)
  - Tufts: The Total University in Changing Times, 1973; MS224.002.013.00037; Tufts University Steering Committee (Box 13)
  - Coonamessett and follow on, MS224.002.013.00038 (Box 13)
  - Tufts University School of Medicine School Dental Medicine: A Plan to Meet Facility Needs, 1969; MS224.002.014.00001; Cresap, McCormick and Paget, Inc. (Box 14)
  - The Quincy School Complex, 1969; MS224.002.014.00002; Quincy School Community Council; Tufts-New England Medical Center Planning Office Quincy School Project Staff (Box 14)
  - Synopsis of Education for the Health Professions, 1974; MS224.002.014.00003; Committee of Presidents of the Health Professions Educational Associations of the Association for the Academic Health Centers (Box 14)
  - The Quincy School Project - Final Report Year One, 1967; MS224.002.014.00004; Kibbe, Frank W., Jr. (Box 14)
  - T-NEMC Andover Planning Conference, 1968; MS224.002.014.00005 (Box 14)
  - Preliminary Architectural Program for the Proposed Medical Educational Buidling, Tufts University School of Medicine, 1969; MS224.002.014.00006; Tufts-New England Medical Center Planning Office (Box 14)
  - Draft Environmental Impact Report for the NEMCH, 1975; MS224.002.014.00007 (Box 14)
  - A Proposal for the Construction of Parking Facilities at the Tufts-New England Medical Center, 1969; MS224.002.014.00008; Tufts-New England Medical Center Planning Office (Box 14)
  - Report on T-NEMC Utility Allocation, 1974; MS224.002.014.00009; R.G. Vanderwil Engineers, Inc. (Box 14)
  - Mixed-Use Developments: New Ways of Land Use, 1976; MS224.002.014.00010; Urban Land Institute (Box 14)
  - T-NEMC Annual Progress Report, 1976 -- 1977; MS224.002.014.00011 (Box 14)
  - T-NEMC Annual Report, 1976; MS224.002.014.00012 (Box 14)
  - Vibration Observations T-NEMC, 1977; MS224.002.014.00013 (Box 14)
  - T-NEMC Laboratory Animal Medicine Income and Expenses, 1977 -- 1978; MS224.002.014.00014 (Box 14)
  - Sprague Construction Company Contract, 1971; MS224.002.014.00015 (Box 14)
  - Inspection Services, MS224.002.014.00016 (Box 14)
  - Phase I Feasibility Report, 1978; MS224.002.014.00017 (Box 14)
  - Parking and Properties, 1977 -- 1978; MS224.002.014.00018 (Box 14)
  - Parking and Properties, 1976 -- 1977; MS224.002.015.00001 (Box 15)
  - Observations and Recommendations on the Organization and the Program of the New England Medical Center, 1958; MS224.002.015.00002; Hinsey, Joseph C. (Box 15)
  - T-NEMC Report on Examination of Financial Statements, 1975; MS224.002.015.00003 (Box 15)
  - T-NEMC Report on Examination of Financial Statements, 1973; MS224.002.015.00004 (Box 15)
  - Memoranda: H.L. Bogen Architect and Planner, 1959; MS224.002.015.00005 (Box 15)
  - Boston and Beyond, MS224.002.015.00006 (Box 15)
  - NEMCH: Facilities Development Project, 1974; MS224.002.015.00007 (Box 15)
  - T-NEMC: Utility Study, 1968; MS224.002.015.00008 (Box 15)
  - T-NEMC: Analysis of Alternate Systems, MS224.002.015.00009; Ross and Baruzzini, Inc. (Box 15)
  - Development of T-NEMC, 1965 -- 1985; MS224.002.015.00010 (Box 15)
  - T-NEMC: Phase I-A, 1982; MS224.002.015.00011; Tufts-New England Medical Center Planning Office (Box 15)
  - T-NEMC: Financial Statements, MS224.002.015.00012 (Box 15)
  - T-NEMC: Annual Report, 1976; MS224.002.015.00013 (Box 15)
  - T-NEMC, Inc., MS224.002.015.00014 (Box 15)
  - Urban Hospital Design in America, 1966; MS224.002.015.00015; Architectural Press Ltd (Box 15)
  - T-NEMC: Construction, 1930 -- 1931; MS224.002.015.00016 (Box 15)
  - T-NEMCH - Columbia Point Health Center Reports and Publications, MS224.002.015.00017 (Box 15)
  - Publications belong to Jerome P. Kassirer, MS224.002.015.00018 (Box 15)
  - Publications, MS224.002.015.00019 (Box 15)
  - Construction employement reports, 1971 -- 1972; MS224.002.015.00020 (Box 15)
  - PC/NECH Minutes of the Administrative Committee of the Executive Staff of the Medical Staff, 1948 -- 1950; MS224.002.015.00021 (Box 15)
  - PC/NECH Minutes of the Administrative Committee of the Executive Staff of the Medical Staff, 1953; MS224.002.015.00022 (Box 15)
  - PC/NECH Minutes of the Administrative Committee of the Executive Staff of the Medical Staff, 1954; MS224.002.015.00023 (Box 15)
  - PC/NECH Minutes of the Administrative Committee of the Executive Staff of the Medical Staff, 1955; MS224.002.015.00024 (Box 15)
  - PC/NECH Minutes of the Administrative Committee of the Executive Staff of the Medical Staff, 1956; MS224.002.015.00025 (Box 15)
  - PC/NECH Minutes of the Administrative Committee of the Executive Staff of the Medical Staff, 1956; MS224.002.015.00026 (Box 15)
  - PC/NECH Minutes of the Administrative Committee of the Executive Staff of the Medical Staff, 1957; MS224.002.015.00027 (Box 15)
  - PC/NECH Minutes of the Administrative Committee of the Executive Staff of the Medical Staff, 1957; MS224.002.015.00028 (Box 15)
  - PC/NECH Minutes of the Administrative Committee of the Executive Staff of the Medical Staff, 1958; MS224.002.015.00029 (Box 15)
  - PC/NECH Minutes of the Administrative Committee of the Executive Staff of the Medical Staff, 1958 -- 1959; MS224.002.015.00030 (Box 15)
  - NEMC Minutes of Administrative Board and its Executive Committee, 1954 -- 1955; MS224.002.015.00031 (Box 15)
  - NEMC Minutes of Administrative Board and its Executive Committee, 1956; MS224.002.015.00032 (Box 15)
  - NEMC Minutes of Administrative Board and its Executive Committee, 1958; MS224.002.016.00001 (Box 16)
  - NEMC Minutes of Administrative Board and its Executive Committee, 1959; MS224.002.016.00002 (Box 16)
  - NEMC Minutes of Administrative Board and its Executive Committee, 1960; MS224.002.016.00003 (Box 16)
  - NEMC Minutes of Administrative Board and its Executive Committee, 1961; MS224.002.016.00004 (Box 16)
  - NEMC Minutes of Administrative Board and its Executive Committee, 1962 -- 1968; MS224.002.016.00005 (Box 16)
  - NEMC Building Committee, 1929 -- 1931; MS224.002.016.00006 (Box 16)
  - T-NEMC Administrative Committee Minutes, 1966 -- 1968; MS224.002.016.00007 (Box 16)
  - T-NEMC Administrative Committee Minutes, 1970 -- 1975; MS224.002.016.00008 (Box 16)
  - T-NEMC Administrative Committee Minutes, 1971 -- 1972; MS224.002.016.00009 (Box 16)
  - T-NEMC Administrative Committee Minutes, 1969 -- 1970; MS224.002.016.00010 (Box 16)
  - T-NEMC Administrative Committee Minutes, 1975 -- 1976; MS224.002.016.00011 (Box 16)
  - T-NEMC Administrative Committee Minutes, 1973 -- 1974; MS224.002.016.00012 (Box 16)
  - Married Student Housing, 1969; MS224.002.016.00013 (Box 16)
  - Health Care Accessibility for Boston's Chinese Community, 73-147-010 and 74-147-006, 1975; MS224.002.017.00001 (Box 17)
  - To Facilitate Health - A proposal to establish Health Facilities Research Inc., 1971; MS224.002.017.00002; Maloney, William F.; Pollack, Jerome; Field, Hermann H. (Box 17)
  - A Tradition of Concern, 1979; MS224.002.017.00003 (Box 17)
  - NEMCH Planning Programs, 1970; MS224.002.017.00004; Tufts-New England Medical Center Planning Office (Box 17)
  - Adaptive Housing for the Handicapped, 1971; MS224.002.017.00005; Fishman, Paul L. (Box 17)
  - Sampan, 1983; MS224.002.017.00006; Chinese-American Civic Association (Box 17)
  - Tufts Journal, 1983; MS224.002.017.00007 (Box 17)
  - The Boston Globe, 1982; MS224.002.017.00008 (Box 17)
    Pages 1-20 only.
  - Boston Herald clipping, 1983; MS224.002.017.00009 (Box 17)
  - Tufts University Health Science News, 1983; MS224.002.017.00010 (Box 17)
  - The Campaign for Tufts, 1983; MS224.002.017.00011 (Box 17)
  - Boston and Beyond, MS224.002.017.00012 (Box 17)
  - T-NEMC, Inc., MS224.002.017.00013 (Box 17)
  - Draft Environmental Impact Report for NEMCH's Facilities Development Program, 1975; MS224.002.017.00014; Environmental Research and Technology, Inc. (Box 17)
  - NECH Inpatient Admission Survey Report, 1969; MS224.002.017.00015; Tufts-New England Medical Center Planning Office (Box 17)
  - Report on Recreation Facilities, 1967; MS224.002.017.00016; Tufts-New England Medical Center Planning Office (Box 17)
  - Rehabilitation Facilities for the Physically Disabled: Places for Transitional Care, 1977; MS224.002.017.00017; Green, Mitchell Lewis (Box 17)
  - NEMC information on patient care, research programs, and education activities, 1981 -- 1983; MS224.002.017.00018 (Box 17)
  - Personnel Policies NEMCH, MS224.002.017.00019 (Box 17)
  - National Hospital Week, 1960; MS224.002.017.00020 (Box 17)
  - NEMCH Employee Recognition Day, 1975; MS224.002.017.00021 (Box 17)
  - Your Rights as a Patient, MS224.002.017.00022 (Box 17)
  - T-NEMC, MS224.002.017.00023 (Box 17)
  - T-NEMC Deptartment of Therapeutic Radiology, 1970; MS224.002.017.00024 (Box 17)
  - New House Staff, 1974; MS224.002.017.00025 (Box 17)
  - Observations and Recommendations on the Organization and the Program of the New England Medical Center, 1958; MS224.002.017.00026; Hinsey, Joseph C. (Box 17)
  - T-NEMC: ProForma Combined Financial Statements, 1962; MS224.002.017.00027 (Box 17)
  - T-NEMC examination for the year ended, 1962 -- 1967; MS224.002.017.00028 (Box 17)
    Non-consecutive.
  - Publicity, 1958 -- 1959; MS224.002.017.00029 (Box 17)
  - Newspaper Releases, 1949 -- 1954; MS224.002.017.00030 (Box 17)
  - Executive Summary, 1980; MS224.002.017.00031; Corcoran, Paul J.; Fay, Frederick A. (Box 17)
  - Boston and Beyond, MS224.002.017.00032 (Box 17)
  - Mothers Help Care for Sick Children in Experimental Unit, 1964; MS224.002.017.00033; Katz, Geneva (Box 17)
  - T-NEMC: Development of Associated Health Education Organization, 1976; MS224.002.017.00034 (Box 17)
  - NEMCH: Medical Service Directory, 1975 -- 1976; MS224.002.017.00035 (Box 17)
- Cancer Center, 1972 -- 1985; MS224.003; 4.8 Linear Feet
  This series contains correspondence, grant proposals, progress reports, and budget reports of various operating accounts at the Cancer Center. There are some monographs relating to breast cancer research included in this series.
  Some folders are water damaged, and should be handled carefully. Financial information is restricted.
  According to Dave Nathan's Guide to the NEMC Archives, the following items are missing:
  Core Grant renewal 1982 (Marchant)
  Site visit videotapes 1983 – Drs. Grossman & Levy
  Correspondence 1978-1983
  Financial records of the Cancer Center and Dana Farber Cancer Control Program
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged alphabetically. Note that at the NEMC archives, records for this series were arranged into groups reflecting the chronological history of the Cancer Center and its successive iterations. This order has been maintained.
  - Breast Cancer Network: New England Network Demonstration Project in Breast Cancer, 1974 -- 1983; MS224.003.001
    - American Radium Society presentation, 1980; MS224.003.018.00001 (Box 18)
      Breast Cancer Network: New England Network Demonstration Project in Breast Cancer
    - Awarded contract, 1979 -- 1980; MS224.003.018.00002 (Box 18)
    - Committee on forms, statistics, and evaluation, 1975 -- 1976; MS224.003.018.00003 (Box 18)
    - Correspondence, 1974; MS224.003.018.00004 (Box 18)
    - Correspondence, 1975; MS224.003.018.00005 (Box 18)
    - Correspondence, 1976; MS224.003.018.00006 (Box 18)
    - Correspondence, 1977; MS224.003.018.00007 (Box 18)
    - Correspondence, 1978; MS224.003.018.00008 (Box 18)
    - Correspondence, 1979; MS224.003.018.00009 (Box 18)
    - Correspondence, 1980; MS224.003.018.00010 (Box 18)
    - Correspondence, 1981; MS224.003.018.00011 (Box 18)
    - Correspondence, 1983; MS224.003.018.00012 (Box 18)
    - Data audits: B.E. Kreger, M.D., 1981; MS224.003.018.00013 (Box 18)
    - Data collection forms, MS224.003.018.00014 (Box 18)
    - Data gatherers guidelines/data definitions, 1977; MS224.003.018.00015 (Box 18)
    - Executive committee, 1980; MS224.003.018.00016 (Box 18)
    - New England network demonstration project in breast cancer final report, 1978; MS224.003.018.00017 (Box 18)
    - New England network demonstration project in breast cancer treatment guidelines, MS224.003.018.00018 (Box 18)
    - Original contract proposal, 1974; MS224.003.018.00019 (Box 18)
    - Progress reports, 1976; MS224.003.018.00020 (Box 18)
    - The Breast Cancer Networks: Organizing to Improve Management of a Disease, 1981; MS224.003.018.00021; Kane, Rosalie A.; Kane, Robert L.; Williams, Christine E.; Hopwood, Marsha D.; Lincoln, Thomas L.; Rettig, Richard A.; Williams, Albert P. (Box 18)
    - New England Prototype Network Demonstration Project in Breast Cancer, 1978; MS224.003.018.00022; Marchant, Douglas J.; Neurath, Peter (Box 18)
      Breast Cancer Network: New England Network Demonstration Project in Breast Cancer Article reprinted from CANCER, vol. 41, no. 3.
    - Teaching module for breast self exam, MS224.003.018.00023 (Box 18)
    - T-NEMC Times, 1975; MS224.003.018.00024 (Box 18)
      Breast Cancer Network: New England Network Demonstration Project in Breast Cancer Blurb publicizing network page 12.
  - Office of Cancer Control - Cancer Center Institute, 1972 -- 1985; MS224.003.002
    - Affiliations - Brockton Hospital, 1980; MS224.003.018.00025 (Box 18)
      Office of Cancer Control - Cancer Center Institute
    - Ancillary staff seminar presentation outline, 1983; MS224.003.018.00026 (Box 18)
    - Bloedorn, Fernando, MS224.003.018.00027 (Box 18)
    - Breast Health Day, 1981-06-24; MS224.003.018.00028; New England Medical Center Cancer Division (Box 18)
      Office of Cancer Control - Cancer Center Institute Breast Cancer Seminar Channel 7 Six O'clock News
      videocassettes
    - Budget projections - all funding sources, 1979 -- 1984; MS224.003.018.00029 (Box 18)
    - Cancer Center correspondence, 1980 -- 1984; MS224.003.019.00001 (Box 19)
    - Cancer Center questionnaire, 1980 -- 1981; MS224.003.019.00002 (Box 19)